<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts of a life wanderer on Jo&#39;s odyssey</title>
    <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts of a life wanderer on Jo&#39;s odyssey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:50:19 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jostorre.me/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Journey</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/myjourney/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 21:20:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/myjourney/</guid>
      <description>Once a wise person told me: the 20&amp;rsquo;s is a very important phase in your life, on top of which the rest of your life will be built. If you make nothing, it&amp;rsquo;ll be hard when you hit 30, but if you make the most out of it, you&amp;rsquo;ll be good. I won&amp;rsquo;t say I had done everything right, but I&amp;rsquo;m trying my best and as far as I am I don&amp;rsquo;t regret a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wishlist</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 17:40:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/wishlist/</guid>
      <description>Just if you were wondering&amp;hellip; here&amp;rsquo;s my wishlist:
 Fjallraven Anorak David Clark Headset Stanley Thermo Gopro Stick Nero TX earphones  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flightreflection</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/flightreflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 12:33:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/flightreflection/</guid>
      <description>How could your fking EGO die on a tuesday? We give so much as forefit Dont be afraid of diyng, be afraid of reaching death unprepared or being the indifferent outside who doesn&amp;rsquo;t value what he has. Don&amp;rsquo;t take anything for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probsandbless</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/probsandbless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 12:32:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/probsandbless/</guid>
      <description>If we think about our problems, almost any problem exists because of the existence of a bigger good that we have. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about any way to solve problems, but about a change of perspective that keeps us from being overwhelmed by a problem and take better decisions by being conscious about what we have.
i.e. any problem relating any friend, could be seen as a blessing because we have a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/random/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:15:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/random/</guid>
      <description>Just some random personal notes on life.
Pleasures  The smell of coffee in the morning. Listen to your favourite song on max volume. Walk on a cold sunny day. The sound of waves breaking against the shore. Warm nights outside. Finish reading a book. Long chats with that person at night. The tiredness after a day of swimming. When your code works. Hug your dog.  Possible Facts  Tuesday is also a good day to start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 23:54:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/simplicity/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash;Still a Draft&amp;ndash;
Stay minimalist; it&amp;rsquo;ll help you focus on the important things.
Last year I only had one pair of shoes. For two years I&amp;rsquo;ve only had one swimming suit. From a friend of mine I learned that one should buy a sweater because one needs to get warm, not because just likes it. I learned from one of my best friends that a carry-on backpack is enough to live a semester abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Languages</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:00:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/languages/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscquotes</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/miscquotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:45:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/miscquotes/</guid>
      <description>Miscelaneous Quote Knowledge Base This is a list of quotes that I&amp;rsquo;ve found during my time living. If they are in this page, it is because they have at least made me thought or question myself (the quotes on this page are not ordered).
Quotes are a great source of inspiration and may be used as an excuse to change our way of living for better. Following, my quote knowledge base:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peoplefirst</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/peoplefirst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 10:39:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/peoplefirst/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not about where, but who with There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why I always save contacts with name and surname; people are important. People are infinite - for sure you might have also heard the phrase &amp;lsquo;each person is a world&amp;rsquo;. Well, for me this phrase is very true. Along our lives we get to know a lot of people. I think there&amp;rsquo;s already studies about that (I&amp;rsquo;ll add the numbers later).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyfe</title>
      <link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/lyfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 10:32:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/lyfe/</guid>
      <description>This is LYFE Life should be written with a Y, to remid us of the joyfullness we should have while living (because the letter Y looks like a person with the arms lifted up to the sky), and to remind to ask ourselves why we are here in this LYFE.
hello! Wake up!
Life is now and you don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss it, because it won&amp;rsquo;t last forever. You have the chance now, use it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
