<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Jose's Universe</title><link>https://jostorre.me/</link><description>Recent content on Jose's Universe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:58:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jostorre.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Studentmenu</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/studentmenu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:58:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/studentmenu/</guid><description>Meal ideas for Student life.
In my daily struggle of not knowing what to cook / eat every day as a student, I think making a menu is a good idea of organizing meals. Here are my meal ideas as a student.
Ez Student Menü Snacks Special Peanut Butter Spread Slice of bread with peanut butter and honey. Unsalted Peanuts &amp;hellip; Breakfast French Toast Bread dipped in scrambled eggs and milk, then fried with butter and served with maple syrup and strawberries.</description></item><item><title>Lifeplan</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:49:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifeplan/</guid><description>There are two quotes that explain why I post this, and why it is useful for you to have a Life Plan.
“Everyone seems to have a clear idea of how other people should lead their lives, but none about his or her own. -Paulo Coehlo. and “Every moment of one&amp;rsquo;s existence one is growing into more or retreating into less.” -N. Mailer.
If we don&amp;rsquo;t have an objective we&amp;rsquo;ll never be able to move forward and therefore won&amp;rsquo;t reach nowhere.</description></item><item><title>Spicyonions</title><link>https://jostorre.me/projects/spicyonions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:45:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/projects/spicyonions/</guid><description>A TOR portable test environment.
TBW (to be written).</description></item><item><title>Norway</title><link>https://jostorre.me/travels/europe/norway/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:45:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/travels/europe/norway/</guid><description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m currently in Trondheim, Norway. I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing about this soon. TBW (to be written).</description></item><item><title>EL Buen Coyote</title><link>https://jostorre.me/projects/ebc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 01:44:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/projects/ebc/</guid><description>Social Coffee Entrepreneurship.
TBW (to be written).</description></item><item><title>Miscquotes</title><link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/miscquotes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:45:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/miscquotes/</guid><description>Miscelaneous Quote Knowledge Base This is a list of quotes that I&amp;rsquo;ve found during my time living. If they are in this page, it is because they have at least made me thought or question myself (the quotes on this page are not ordered).
Quotes are a great source of inspiration and may be used as an excuse to change our way of living for better. Following, my quote knowledge base:</description></item><item><title>Peoplefirst</title><link>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/peoplefirst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 10:39:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/thoughts/peoplefirst/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s not about where, but who with There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why I always save contacts with name and surname; people are important. People are infinite - for sure you might have also heard the phrase &amp;lsquo;each person is a world&amp;rsquo;. Well, for me this phrase is very true. Along our lives we get to know a lot of people. I think there&amp;rsquo;s already studies about that (I&amp;rsquo;ll add the numbers later).</description></item><item><title>Me Myself and I</title><link>https://jostorre.me/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:50:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/about/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, I suppose, is because you got interested and wanted to know more. In this case thanks for gifting me your time and congratulations.
What you see, has been created because of two main reasons:
The need of sharing with others. A great person who inspired me to do this in order to save thoughts and knowledge in order to improve, to whom I dedicate this website.</description></item></channel></rss>