<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Resources for a life on There</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/</link><description>Recent content in Resources for a life on There</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:38:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jostorre.me/assets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crossbackcountryski</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/crossbackcountryski/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 13:29:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/crossbackcountryski/</guid><description>What is that? Well, it is like crosscountry skiing, but with a backpack and offroad. aka: Badass cool shit. Last weekend I had my first cross backcountry skiing experience. It was amazing. Therefore I thought of writing about it in case anyone wants to do it or is about to do it and wants to know how to be prepared. This is based on my experience. Following, I describe the conditions as well as the equipment I took with me that worked.</description></item><item><title>Winterrun</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/winterrun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 13:27:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/winterrun/</guid><description>A year ago I was wondering what gear would I need to run during winter. With winter I mean: Snow and minus degrees. Now, I can tell, based on experience, how it is like to run in the snow, and what kind of equipment is needed to enjoy a nice cold run.
With the following gear I would dare to run from temperatures of -1°C to -12°C.
Gear Technical beanie Bandana Thermal long sleve baselayer t-shirt Running t-shirt Running gloves Running short tights Thermal baselayer legging Socks Winter running spikes Running shoes Wind + Waterproof lightjacket Lipbalm *If you still find it very cold, you can add a thin cotton hoodie, nevertheless I always get very warm after 10 minutes of running without a hoodie.</description></item><item><title>Lifehacks</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifehacks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 23:50:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifehacks/</guid><description>Practical stuff that can upgrade your everyday.
Charge your phone away from your bed at night. Set a timer when taking a shower / getting ready. &amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Morningloading</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/morningloading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 12:11:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/morningloading/</guid><description>Before officially starting a day, I think it is a great idea to consider and reflect a few things. Here I propose some questions to ask before going out of our rooms:
What do I want to accomplish today? Who might be having a hard time today that i can help? With hom haven&amp;rsquo;t I spoken in a long time that I can contact today? What did I miss yesterday that I can do today?</description></item><item><title>Nightbalance</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/nightbalance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 12:11:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/nightbalance/</guid><description>At night, when the day is gone and nothing is left but to sleep to be fully charged for the next day, the next challenge, it is worth having a small reflection to overview how our day has been and how have we been. Here I propose some questions to reflect before going to bed in order to improve:
What have I done today? How much time did I invest in each thing today?</description></item><item><title>Studentmenu</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/studentmenu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:58:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/studentmenu/</guid><description>Meal ideas for Student life.
In my daily struggle of not knowing what to cook / eat every day as a student, I think making a menu is a good idea of organizing meals. Here are my meal ideas as a student.
Snacks Special Peanut Butter Spread Slice of bread with peanut butter and honey. Just Nuts May them be peanuts, cashews or even pistacchios. Dark Chocolate 70% Cacao Dark Chocolate.</description></item><item><title>Lifeplan</title><link>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifeplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:49:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jostorre.me/assets/lifeplan/</guid><description>There are two quotes that explain why I post this, and why it is useful for you to have a Life Plan.
“Everyone seems to have a clear idea of how other people should lead their lives, but none about his or her own. -Paulo Coehlo. and “Every moment of one&amp;rsquo;s existence one is growing into more or retreating into less.” -N. Mailer.
If we don&amp;rsquo;t have an objective we&amp;rsquo;ll never be able to move forward and therefore won&amp;rsquo;t reach nowhere.</description></item></channel></rss>